he
t
[Music]
w oh
2 o
[Music]
w
he
[Music]
he a
hello everyone and welcome to another
exciting episode of our innovators live
series I'm Chloe Condon and I'm your
host each week as we talk to interesting
people who are doing amazing things with
Google Cloud products and this week is
no exception uh of course this week's
topic is anthropics cloud models on
vertex AI we're going to be talking
about prompt engineering and doing a
deep dive into best practices but let's
go over our agenda today of course uh we
will be doing a Vertex AI overview we're
then going to be doing an anthropic
overview to get an idea of what that is
and how that works we'll then move over
to prompting Claud very exciting topic
and then we'll talk about training
prompts and move on to rag architecture
and tips now remember if you have any
questions today throughout the session
we have a handy dandy chat available and
if one of our moderators doesn't answer
your question then we may answer your
question live on air at the very end of
the stream so make sure to stay tuned
for the whole thing you may see your
question answered live on air so let's
do a little bit of a review of what it
takes to to drive business value with
geni it takes much more than just a
model to be able to do that and within
vertex AI you have access to our agent
Builder our model builder and our model
garden tools so whether you're looking
to prompt or serve or tune uh use our
retrieval engines maybe you want to
train or just need a single place to
discover and customize and deploy a wide
variety of models from Google or from
our Google Partners vertex AI offers
support and we're going to be diving
deeper into a little bit more of that
today but what is it vertex model Garden
of course is a single environment where
you can do everything from search for
models you can use it directly to test
models in an environment you can
finetune and play around and create
models without code and then of course
you can use in notebooks so that means
using our vertex AI workbench and use
models inside of a
notebook and of of course to bring us
full circle to today's topic anthropics
Cloud models are available on vertex AI
model Garden who knew so in order to
supercharge this this power of
anthropics cloud models on vertex Ai and
learn all about prompt engineering we
have an extra special guest in fact this
is an innovators live first we have
someone from anthropic joining us today
to give us the real scoop on the best
practices of how to be using this so
without further Ado I'm going to
introduce Our Guest today welcome Ellie
shopic who is a member of the technical
staff at anthropic welcome Ellie thank
you so much Chloe for having me I'm
super excited to be here talk a little
bit about how you can use anthropic on
vertex a little bit more about our
company and then really dive into prompt
engineering which gonna really try to do
my best to turn this more into a science
and a little bit less of maybe the art
form that you might think so without
further Ado I just want to hop for a
quick second and talk about who we are
sure many of you are familiar with the
models that we have but who we are as a
company we are an AI safety and research
lab and our mission is to ensure trans
formative AI helps people and Society
flourish we do that by building Frontier
systems and also studying them working
responsibly to deploy them and are being
very intentional with the research and
science that we share our goal is to
create models that are helpful harmless
and honest and we do our absolute best
in the training and fine-tuning process
to ensure that is the case while also
building very highly intelligent
Frontier models we've been really really
proud of the ability that we've had to
to innovate as not a lot of time has
gone on so really since uh 2023 when we
launched some of the much earlier models
all the way until now it's been only
about three months from launching the
Claud 3 family of models Haiku Sonet and
Opus to our latest and most intelligent
model CLA 35 Sonet so something we're
really proud of is in just such a short
period of time we're able to really keep
up with a tremendous amount of
innovation in the space and in many
cases lead a lot of that innovation in
geni some of the things that you might
not know about anthropic one of the uh
most important AI Innovations of 2023 as
per Time Magazine is a process called
constitutional Ai and constitutional AI
is where we take in some of the most
well uh thought out and discussed
principles and documents that we as a
society have generated so the UN
Declaration of Human Rights Apple's
terms of service and we train a special
model on that to help anthropic models
become harmful harmless helpful and
honest so this is a really powerful
Innovation that we've made that allows
our models to have more aligned outputs
improved outputs and focus on that
Honesty helpfulness and
harmlessness as you've seen many times
in the geni space there are many
different models there are many
different use cases for families of
models so in the Enterprise AI space
there are many different constraints
that you might face from cost to latency
or speed as well as intelligence so in
the cloud family of models we have quite
a few targeting some of the more complex
and more intelligent requiring tasks
like agents to some of the tools like a
basic chat where you want to focus on
your efficiency and speed and minimize
cost and with that we have our family of
models we have Claud 3 Hau which is our
fastest most compact model so sitting
kind of in that corner of the
intelligence and cost chart here we have
our Claude 35 Sonet which is our most
intelligent model that we recently
released that allows kind of the The
Best of Both Worlds as well as claw 3
Opus which is excellent at writing and
more complex tasks a little bit more on
the costly end but very intelligent as
well so just to give you a I have to say
I love these these naming conventions
I'm noticing a little bit of a theme a
sonnet Haiku and Opus yeah very very
very much so yeah really really leans
into the uh the length that you're going
to be dealing with and a lot of the
examples that we have and you can look
in the documentation for kind of what
we're dealing with for how long it's
going to take to read through a book or
read through a sonnet or an or a haiku
so definitely leaning into terminology
as we keep evolving our models
absolutely so what can you do with Claud
what can you do with many different
things in the Gen AI ecosystem
specifically with Claude 3.5 Sonet there
are a lot of really powerful examples
and in our documentation we are
constantly updating with use case guides
as well as more technical notebooks for
text generation content moderation
coding relating tasks classification we
just launch a couple new use case guides
especially in the classification and
ticket routing side of things and we'll
keep doing more and more of that but as
there's more and more rapid innovation
in this space there's just more and more
that you can do with these models which
is incredibly exciting to us as a
company some of the things that you may
have been kind of diving into and Khloe
mentioned this a little bit with the
agentic capabilities some of the models
especially Opus as well as 3.5 Sonet
have increased agentic capabilities and
just to give you a quick overview of the
idea of an agent this is where we can
assign some kind of task to a model have
the model perform the necessary steps
make the necessary function calls or API
calls or routing to figure out the right
Next Step all programmatically and all
done through generative AI so as these
models continue to get more intelligent
more efficient this is only a pattern
that we're going to just keep following
more and more and more of and there are
many different infrastructures for
creating agents these can be done
programmatically on your own so many
different ways to kind of offer these
agentic capabilities which is something
that just seeing more and more of in
this
space with that said I want to shift
gears a little bit and I want to talk
about something that feels relatively
basic and in fact it's not the most
complex thing but it's really a matter
of figuring out the right Tech
techniques and best practices a lot of
times when you hear prompt engineering
you might go towards the engineering
side of things and I want to lean more
towards just techniques and best
practices for getting the right thing or
getting the thing you want out of the
model A lot of these tactics are going
to be a bit specific to Claude but if
you are working with other large
language models a lot of these
techniques still apply so there might be
things that you've heard of a bit before
and there might be things that hopefully
you're going to learn about as we talk
about prompting Claud so at a very high
overview I'm sure many of you know this
but let's make sure we got our
terminology down what is a prompt it's
the information you pass to an llm large
language model to get back a response
and what you pass inside of this prompt
determines the response that you get not
just the question that you're asking but
also some context about that question
maybe some data some examples some
instructions there's so much that goes
into a prompt so how do you engineer a
good prompt the same way that you would
really think about engineering good code
and with that you think about your
testing first you think about your edge
cases first so very commonly when we
have companies that are working with us
and using our models we really do our
absolute best to move from instead of an
form treat this like a science develop
test cases don't forget about your edge
cases and think about when there is a
prompt what is the ideal output or the
golden output as we say you can start by
engineering some preliminary prompt you
can test it against use cases and then
you can refine The Prompt this part of
the prompt engineering life cycle is by
far the most important because if you go
ahead and switch to a different model if
you go ahead and even use an entirely
different large language model or a
different version of an existing model
how do you know if the prompts that you
have in production potentially are going
to do any better or any worse and that's
where the entire process of evals or
evaluations comes into play we'll talk
about those at a high level but
hopefully you'll get to invite me back
and I can talk about evals in
depth so think of your evals as really
just a a unit test if I put in this
prompt and I asked this prompt some
specific piece of information do I get
the answer back that I expect and as I
do at over hundreds or thousands of test
prompts am I getting consistent results
what percentage of accuracy am I getting
I can also measure things like latency
or the speed can also be mindful of how
many tokens are being used from a cost
perspective so you can really do a lot
of engineering here to make sure that
the prompts that you produce hold out
against your evals and are ready to get
into production and we're not looking
for exact uh matches each time I imagine
because I know when I'm prompting AI
sometimes look at a slightly slightly
different but same answer but not the
same wording we're just trying to see if
we're getting the outcome we write want
right absolutely so it's a it's an
excellent question because it really as
with many things in gen it depends on
your use case so in the in the in this
essence of something like text
summarization it would be really really
really hard to say it must look the
summary must look exactly like this
that's where you need to use either
large language models to help you with
your eval or potential string matching
or patterns for just looking for
particular things if it's a case of
maybe classification where the answer is
either something from a category or some
specific data structure that you know
what it's going to look like you might
have a chance to do a bit more of that
exact matching but your spoton with not
every single use case is always going to
be a perfect match sometimes it's
something similar and that's where you
have to iterate and it all depends on
your use case that's an excellent point
as a developer relations engineer that
is always fun when it comes uh when it
comes to making documentation I think
we're so used to saying this output will
happen but since AI is learning all the
time it's been an interesting thing to
adjust to just like you said prompting
is deceptively uh it's not as simple as
I think people paint it out to be
absolutely yeah and I'm I'm excited to
show you actually as we get into some of
those tools to to make this a little bit
easier to work with because many times
you might read some documentation you
might read some guides on prompting and
best practices and they might actually
point you towards something that feels a
bit like this you want to put in your
prompt the context for your task you
want to put in the tone you want to
think about background data and examples
and a history and thinking step by step
and don't forget to make sure that your
model knows how to think and think about
pre-filling and it's going to get really
really hard to keep that all in your
brain or memorize some kind of acronym
for all the things that you need or
think about all the colors that we have
here so the way that we think about
prompt engineering at anthropic
especially for our customers is don't
start from scratch we already have lots
of good practices we already have lots
of good ideas for how best to work with
these models so instead let's actually
start in reverse and we've introduced a
tool here and I'm going to show you in a
second called The Meta prompter and what
we actually have here is you as the user
put in the thing you're trying to do we
then will use Claude to write a prompt
for you with all the best practices that
allows you to then work off of that
prompt and have something that you can
build off of because it's very difficult
to just start engineering with a prompt
from scratch especially if you're even
coming from a different language model
and you're trying to adopt different
practices so let's see what that looks
like G to hop over using AI to help with
our AI prompting yes hence the term meta
prompting exactly that is that is so I
am at the anthropic console that's
console. anthropic tocom and I'm going
to go to the prompt generator or meta
prompter whatever word you want to use
there I'm going to use AI to use AI just
like you said Chloe so you can put in
the particular task that you want at
hand I'm just going to pick one of these
just to show you as an example I'm going
to draft an email responding to a
customer complaint and offer a
resolution let's imagine for some reason
you're very upset with what happens in
this hour and we need Claude to help us
out and offer some resolution but
hopefully that is not the case so we'll
give this a second to kind of work its
magic but what you're going to see here
is a whole bunch of text this is being
generated from Claude and this right
here is a great place for us to start
working
from once we continue we can you can
actually go ahead
and stay here and we're going to be
taken to our workbench this is all
inside of the console and this allows us
to work with the prompt maybe your task
with drafting a professional empathetic
so maybe I don't necessarily want
empathetic I want a strongly worded I
can go ahead and change this as much as
I want what I've gotten out of the box
is just the meta prompter not only can I
start working with this I can go ahead
and just grab the code for that so let's
go ahead and use the vertex AI SDK to do
so and I've got that right here to work
with so a lot of times the the code
necessary to talk to the llm is not
terribly complex but just getting that
boiler plate is really nice can hop to
the docs I can copy that code throw it
in a notebook throw it in a script go on
with my day in this case we're given
some variables so in our prompt we are
given some for example here's what that
complaint might look like here's what
the company name might look like here
are the resolution options if I am just
needing to generate some simple data for
this prompt it's kind of hard for me
even to just think of examples from
scratch so again let's just use
generative AI to help us out walk me
through the logic that you're thinking
about for generating these example
inputs just so that I can have something
to work with so instead of me trying to
write an example of a complaint email
I'm just going to use gen to do
that it's now going to fill in the
blanks here I can actually see the logic
that it's using under the hook could for
generating these examples so the goal
here is to start with something build
for yourself a workbench where you can
actually start putting in some dummy
data and seeing what you get back in
this response we're going to see an
example of this email and here is where
we can take this data and we can
evaluate it against something so in this
case we're not necessarily going to find
the perfect response here but maybe we
want to make sure that we're seeing
things with reply to this email we want
to make sure we're seeing the word
refund credit card and check we want to
make sure that we mention two to three
business days that could be part of our
evaluation Suite talking about
evaluation Suites we can go ahead and
hop to this section here on evaluate and
you can see right here here are the
variables here is the prompt and I can
now go ahead and assign a grade to these
evals I can export these I can import
test cases I can even just generate a
bunch of test cases so for example pick
some new things tell me what the
response is let's go ahead and see what
you get
you can move this to a different place
programmatically you can move this in a
CSV this idea of just building
infrastructure so that you can prompt
the right way is incredibly valuable and
it just helps you not have to do things
from scratch the hardest part with
prompt engineering is you start with
something you build on it you build on
it you build on it you kind of have this
house of cards and then it's not doing
what you want it to do and you don't
necessarily know why so really helpful
to kind of think about the testing first
think about the evaluations first can't
stress that
enough if you feel good about what you
have you're excellent but here's an
opportunity to now compare that to a
different prompt that you have and this
now gives you the ability to run given
these variables different prompts to get
different responses and see which one
works better this is something that even
if you are not necessarily technical
that's not a problem you don't need to
know any python to make this work you
just need to log in and start working
with it so you have a lot of
functionality within this workbench you
also have the ability to tweak many
different things so I'll kind of leave
that to you to explore some more this is
a really powerful tool for just getting
up and running and testing your prompts
and I love that it's all in one place
I'm not having to contact switch or or
click around that I can just have
everything in one spot play around a
little bit compare side by side I have
to say when you showed that rainbow
visual I got very excited as a visual
person if only there was a way to
automate this really really it's a
really really pretty pretty slide which
is why we show it first and then we show
you the meta prompter but yes it is
definitely it's got lots of colors and
it's super pretty but with that comes
the the complexity that you just
mentioned so you could def I was
thinking Roy G Biv anthropic yeah
exactly that is that is spot on so
thankfully we have an easier tool to do
that and that is our our meta prompter
so the idea here again we capture the
best practices we're constantly
iterating on this as we figure out more
and more of the best practices one of
the things that is just a constant era
of or place of Discovery is figuring out
the best ways to prompt these llms
something that is just changing as newer
models are released as different
research techniques are released
different prompting techniques are
released so being able to kind of stay
on top of that without you having to
keep that all in your head can be
extremely extremely
helpful so with that said you're going
to get a prompt generated for you let's
just talk about some of the important
parts of that
prompt when you are prompting you want
to make sure you have some kind of role
and highlevel task for what you would
like the llm to do many times people
kind of take this to an extreme like you
are the smartest mathematician in the
world you have 15 phds from the most
respected institutions in the world you
can solve any math problem there's only
so much hyping up of Claude that you can
do so instead clear and concise and just
stick to the role and the task that you
have at hand right after that you want
to put in your Dynamic content you want
to put in in any external data that you
are retrieving that's where that goes
right there so right under that that's
where the dynamic content in our case
these variables or if you're using rag
which we'll talk about a little bit
later embed that right
here the next step you want to be
mindful of is detailed instructions and
many times you might hear things like
this idea of Chain of Thought or make
sure that you tell your large language
model to think step by step and just
those words think step by step can be
very beneficial but I really want to
push you all to just do a little bit
more instead of just saying think step
by step what are the actual steps what
is the thinking that you want or what is
the thinking that you want to see from
Claud so that you can then get a sense
of in the prompt maybe what you need to
shift to steer CLA in the direction of
the thinking that you might want so
you'll see when you generate those meta
prompts or even when writing prompts on
your own thinking step byep can be
extremely helpful but you really want to
lean more into that piece
step that you want to get to you'll see
this idea with endot prompting three
shot five shot 10 shot sounds like a Dr
Seuss book but this is endot prompting
or the number of examples that you want
to provide examples can be extremely
extremely helpful especially when you
want things to follow an exact path or
kind of rigid output or structure there
is no one magical answer for the exact
number of examples that you need but to
start 3 to five is a great
place if there are critical instru
put them at the end and repeat them and
that can be extremely extremely helpful
for just staying on
task another piece that you're going to
see a lot in Claude prompts are XML tags
for those of you not familiar with XML
you might be familiar with HTML these
are just tags that you use to build web
pages and XML tags follow a very similar
structure you just pick the name of the
tags so instead of H1 div body span you
get to make them up the purpose of these
XML tags tags is to help Claude
comprehend the organization of your data
Claude is trained on XML tags it's also
trained on a tremendous amount of things
on the internet and HTML so it has the
ability to figure out in terms of where
you want to put your data XML tags are a
very very helpful way to do that they're
not necessarily required but it's a
really wise idea especially as you have
much larger prompts to help Cloud
organize its thinking for knowing what
goes where
as we mentioned with these examples you
really want to lean into the relevance
of your examples obviously you want an
example that's going to indicate what
you're looking for but you also want to
think a lot about the diversity of
examples so if you're just providing the
same example over and over again but
You' change one or two things that might
not be the most helpful so think a lot
especially with potential edge cases
without the diversity of your examples
many times instead of just giving
examples in a lot of depth it can be
helpful to just show CL what you are
trying to get out so instead of trying
to describe your example with all this
text sometimes it's as simple as here's
the input I want here's the output I
want here's the question I want here's
the answer I want so this is also where
being a little bit more on the shorter
and concise part can be very beneficial
one of the things that we see a lot of
times with prompts when we are debugging
or triaging prompts and we'll talk about
that a little bit are just these massive
prompts that have so much text that you
would look at and just say I have no
idea what to do with this thing
and that's actually where the golden
rule of prompting came to be the golden
rule of prompting is again this is going
to sound very simple but you'd be
shocked can you take the prompt that
you've written can you hand it to the
person next to you in front of you
behind you above you and can they just
understand what you're trying to do
sometimes debugging a prompt is really
as simple as can you just do that part
because a lot of prompts get really
unwieldy you might have tons of
conditional logic or all sorts of fancy
things you're trying to do a lot of
times those don't really move the needle
the sometimes even hurt
you another piece that you might have
seen before and you can see this with a
lot of different large language models
is you can start to put words in
claude's mouth this can be very helpful
for steering the behavior having control
over the format but what you can do is
in the assistant field the way that
Claude works is you have a user who puts
in some content and then the assistant
is what Claude gives you back you can
actually start by pre-filling claud's
response you can give it the start of
the J output that you want you can give
it the start of the XML tag you're
looking for you can give it the start of
some Preamble so that Claud kind of
picks up where you left off so depending
on your use case you can really be
mindful of if I'm not getting things
that I want in a particular Lane can you
start to give CLA kind of a A little
nudge for here's where I want you to
begin you take over from here it's
almost like doing a group project with
with CLA I did the first C here's the
rest and the good news is actually have
to work that hard on the group project
and you can still get get an excellent
grade so you can be that that person in
the was in
school when you think about things like
rag Dynamic data like we mentioned you
want to put that long information at the
top after you specify your role and this
actually does make a difference in the
quality of your prompts and the outputs
that you get so this is one of those
places where order can be very important
again if you don't remember it that's
all good that's what the meta prompter
is there
for when you're working with long
context when you have a lot of
information a lot of text inside of one
prompt or you're retrieving lots of
examples and you just have a ton a ton a
ton of text to minimize hallucinations
to minimize the llm saying something
that may be incorrect or even saying I
don't know you can ask Claude to find
relevant quotes before answering you can
also ask Claude to share those quotes
with you so that you have citations you
can stay a little bit more grounded in
the truth you can also have Claud read
the document carefully because it will
be asked questions later and you might
look at this and say well it's not like
Claude is GNA take 10 more seconds to
read the document because I said so but
again little things like this can really
move the
needle and does that help with
efficiency like being able to to get to
the answer faster or maybe you know
doing more of a a breath verus versus a
depth search in this instance or why are
definitely more of the more of the
breath there we're really just trying to
stay grounded in accuracy so we're
really just trying to do everything we
can to preempt the model to give us the
most accurate response and that's kind
of worthy sometimes Thinking by thinking
step by step can produce better quality
answers saying things like read the
document carefully because I'm going to
ask you questions about it can produce
answers that are either grounded or
prompts clawed to say things like I
don't know which can be equally as
valuable because the you know nothing
nothing is worse than your model saying
something that is just clearly not true
because every model gives every answer
with the utmost confidence we don't
really have a kind of confidence meter
out of the box that uh that we can get
so this is where just focusing on that
kind of breath I would say so that you
make sure that it's going to give you
the most grounded answer is H is where
we're getting to it's like telling
Claude there will be a test well there
there you go exactly the same way that
if you're in a classroom and the teacher
says there's gonna be a quiz at the end
of this you're probably more likely to
listen to what the teacher has to say so
that's that's my bad I should have said
there was going to be a quiz before I
started
some best practices as you start working
with large language models provide as
much situational context as possible so
when we talk about that kind of role
that you're talking about instead of
just asking Claude for something try to
give Claude some context for who you are
what information's useful what you need
or if this is for a customer any
customer specific context for example a
decent prompt might just say something
like explain to me in brief how rag
works and you'll probably get a pretty
decent answer but but depending on the
kind of answer that you want granted yes
this does take a little bit more text to
put in and again The Meta prompter can
be very helpful but really kind of
setting the stage for what you want the
output to be this can save you a lot of
back and forth with the llm because many
times you might just say something like
explain rag to me okay that was good but
I'm an account executive and I'm
preparing for a meeting try it again oh
actually the clients in the financial
sector so try it again um actually make
your answer pretty convincing this is
where just providing that situational
context thinking a little bit more
before you jump to get an answer out can
be really really
helpful as we talk a little bit about
those thinking instructions remember
telling Claude to think step by step
telling your model to think step by step
can be beneficial and has been shown to
be beneficial in very interesting papers
but as we kind of go to the next step
around that we want to think a lot about
not just tell Cloud to think but how
should Claude think what are any details
what are any steps what is the thinking
process you want Claude to take the same
way that if you're trying to teach
something to someone you might just not
tell them go solve the problem you might
say something like show your work or go
through it step by step here are the
steps that I want you to take so for
example how can we make this a little
bit better with some thought
instructions we're getting to the role
we're talking about who we are and then
we're doing a pretty nice job for hey I
have a general understanding of AI but
no technical background so you don't
need to explain rag to me as if I don't
know anything about AI I need to be able
to explain this to an audience that's
non-technical while addressing concerns
for technical folks so how can we make
this better with some thought
instructions let's go ahead and take a
look at one example here granted you
look at this and it's a oh man there's
just like a lot of text I need to write
sometimes yeah Again The Meta prompter
can be very helpful for that but when
you are going through prompts yourself
can be really useful to kind of dive
into what's happening here so bring
storm the information that would be most
important and then be sure to account
for these things and then brainstorm
what information I can highlight the
reason why this is also very beneficial
is because you can ask Claude to Output
its thought in thinking tags in a
scratchpad tag whatever you want to
choose for your tag and you will
actually see what Claude is thinking as
it gets you an answer and that can be
really beneficial when you go back and
say oh turns out you're actually
thinking about this in a different way
I'd like you to go ahead and change the
way that you're thinking and that's
going to produce a really optimal output
so we've got some really good practices
for building prompts however many times
in the real world you are either given a
prompt or you are working on some
existing prompt and it's not doing what
you want it to do so I want to shift
gears a little bit to triaging prompts
triaging prompts meaning you have a
prompt something's not working what do
you do what info do you need so whether
that's a customer or someone on your
team is just saying the customer is
reporting that the prompt is not doing
what we want it to do what info do you
need first and foremost you want to have
the use case and the prompt so you want
to make sure it's very hard to debug
prompts when you don't actually have the
prompt so if you're just saying hey
we're getting an output of true when it
should be false you want to make sure
you know what's going on here so when
there is a problem make sure you analyze
the full use case and the prompt some
examples and potentially the problematic
output and the ideal in output again
this is where having evals or
evaluations can be really really helpful
so I'm going to talk through this little
piece and then I'm actually going to
show you a course that we have that is
on our courses GitHub that uses vertex
where you can practice yourself for how
to tweak those props so we're going to
step through these triaging processes
and then I'm going to give you a brief
introduction to our course talk about
Rag and we'll have some time for
Q&A first thing again I know it's uh
sometimes seems a bit silly but you'd be
surprised how many people try to just
jump to brainstorming things just read
the prompt does it follow that Golden
Rule can you explain it to the person
next to you do you actually understand
the issue and then think about what
Solutions you might have and if there
are other things you need to think about
get to it but really try to be
scientific in this process does the
prompt make sense again this Golden Rule
here can I give it to someone else if I
receive this prompt as instructions
could I do the task successfully a lot
of this is really just
organization sometimes you might look at
this and say wow you have examples at
the top then you have examples at the
bottom then you have instructions in the
middle and you have instructions at the
bottom that seem to contradict the
instructions in the middle when these
prompts get bigger and bigger and bigger
as you try to just handle more and more
and more many cases these are actually
the problems that you run
into again make sure you understand the
issue identify the possible cause is
Claud trying to be too helpful is Claud
not helpful enough are there no explicit
instructions on how to ground its
response in the truth this is really the
number one thing for minimizing
hallucinations you have to ask Claud to
check its work you have to ask Claud to
provide citations you have to ask CLA
sometimes if you really don't know say I
don't know if there is a low accuracy
here are some really good questions to
dive into and many times it's it's
really as simple as these first couple
things is your prompt just way too big
are there way too many complicated
instructions could a human look at this
and just say I have no idea where to
even start is there a lack of Specific
Instructions many times many different
people work on the same prompt and they
find that that they're actually
repeating themselves with slightly
different wording and that just reduces
the accuracy because you're trying to
just have Claude do too much so a lot of
times it's really just reading
dissecting thinking about those best
practices even taking the task running
through the meta prompter and just
comparing side by side what's the meta
prompter giving me what does my
structure look like where can I begin
there is Claude mistaking a harmless
task as harmful like I mentioned we
spend a lot of time and a lot of thought
into refusals into making sure that
things that are not appropriate are not
being used in any way in our ecosystem
that does open the opportunity for a
potential harmless task as harmful are
there ways that we can be mindful to
steer CLA in prefilling the response or
in the text of the prompt for making
sure that we're getting things that may
actually be totally harmless to not have
Claud kind of come in and think that
it's
harmful do we have enough examples does
the prompt have a clear structure so
many times really just these relatively
simple things that cause a lot of
problems a lot of
headache if Claude is trying to be
overly helpful tell it had to be helpful
while being accurate tell it had to say
I don't know be short and succinct if
there's no instruction for how to ground
things in the truth just like we saw get
quotes answer based on the quotes show
those quotes site your sources same way
you'd ask someone if they're presenting
something where you getting that
information from site your sources have
Cloud check over its own work as
well what I want to do for one brief
moment is actually take a step back and
think about why the answer you get from
an llm might not actually be what you
expect at the end of the day the way
that these models work is a very kind of
fancy sounding process called autor
regressive generation which is simply
just taking in some input and figuring
out the highest probability for the very
first small piece of
output and then we take the next step
and do the exact same thing and the next
step and do the exact same thing thing
and do the next step and do the exact
same thing and we do that until we
either finish the response or run out of
tokens or someone tells us to stop but
it's simply just this process of seeing
what we've done before and recalculating
over and over again for the next thing
the reason why it's so important to have
this mental model is because when you
get an output when you get a response
from an llm it's not just all coming at
once it is actually step by step figured
out what is the next word what's the
next piece of the word what's the next
piece of the word what's the next piece
of the word so when you are debugging a
particular output try to think for
yourself how did I get to this output
how did I end up with the very last
character the very last token the very
last word even in the particular output
that I had it's because the thing before
it said the most likely thing that
follows is what you're seeing so think
about your outputs from llms as being
generated step by step and there is some
reason why it got to that step so maybe
instead of just looking at the last
thing the model gives you take a look at
the entire output and see maybe where
things went wrong and that's where you
can debug
appropriately many different reasons why
things can get better Cloud doesn't
understand there are not enough examples
The Prompt lost lacks structure and so
on many different issues many different
solutions that you can look into we have
a lot of all this good stuff in the
course that I'm going to share so I'll
go through this relatively quickly like
we mentioned pre-filling responses more
examples are better prlax clear
structure create those set C with XML
TX once you've got some improvements
what do you go and delete what do you go
and rewrite kind of like with code
sometimes it's really nice to just
delete things and it feels really good
when you just have lots of deletions and
things are shorter and more concise and
readable and such treat your prompts the
same
way again you can always check your
improvements in the console you can
always compare the results using that
evaluation suite and that workbench that
we have if for some reason you need to
break the prompt into smaller prompts
you need an intent classifier there are
many different Advanced Techniques for
dealing with prompting and that's a
whole other discussion for another time
but most of the time before you jump for
things like fine-tuning before you jump
for intend classifiers or other decision
trees or more advanced patterns a lot of
these steps here are going to solve
problems and this is what we've seen
with so many customers that it's
actually these things that get you in
trouble but these things that are also
relatively easy to fix in the scheme of
things
before we shift to rag I want to just
briefly walk through a course that we
have this is on our courses website and
I'll go ahead and share that link with
you make sure you all have it this is a
real world prompting course that we've
made and it uses vertex exclusively I'm
using the command line to log in but you
can do this really anywhere you can put
this in your own notebook you can open
this in a collab but here's the
interface that I'm using it has five
sections the first part is a prompting
recap so very similar to what we talked
about but if you want to see this kind
of in a notebook format you want to see
a little bit more in the screenshots you
want to see some examples of input text
and generated prompts this is a really
good place to start the second section
that we have is an example with a
medical prompt so we are going to take
some of those ideas that we saw in the
first lesson and we're going to use a
real world prompt this is not customer
data by any means this is all just kind
of madeup stuff and synthetic data that
we have here but we're going to go ahead
and take some patient records and we're
going to generate some summaries from
those records we're going to start with
prompts that are not great again I have
this record can you summarize it for me
I need this quickly again you might just
find yourself writing prompts like this
and you might not get the responses that
you
want to give you a little bit of an idea
of how this works with vertex not a
terrible amount of code necessary even
if you've used other sdks or R SDK it's
very similar you go ahead and just use
this create function that's built on our
client messages object and all that
comes in from anthropic vertex so
initialize the enop iic vertex instance
and then go ahead and using the messages
API create a message start a
conversation with the large language
model just to show you what that looks
like I'm going to go ahead and log in
make sure that I'm authenticated before
I go ahead and do that so I'll hop over
here log in with the Google off library
and Chloe I'm sure there are many many
different ways that folks can do this
this is just the the way that I'm
showing you right now but you can do
this in the model Garden you can do this
with Enterprise notebooks you can do
this in collab and authenticate so many
different ways to uh to tackle this
particular
piece once you're logged in you can go
ahead and start calling CLA and here
I'll go ahead and make sure I actually
have those patient records might yell at
me for not having those yet so we'll go
ahead and generate that summary and
here's a summary that we get back so
this is simply just the conversation
that you can have with the llm here's
the code necessary to get up and running
it's relatively minimal because the
focus here is not doing very complex
things with the SDK it's really focusing
on prompting so you can scroll through
you can see some examples of good
prompts and bad prompts you can take a
little bit more in-depth of prompt
engineering and the engineering life
cycle all things that we've spoken about
but if you want to see it again and run
some examples this is a great place to
do so and then we got two sections at
the end one for the call summarizer
which builds up a very simple prompt
into more complicated ideas and then the
last example that I definitely recommend
looking through which is essentially the
triaging of a prompt where we start with
a prompt here's all the information that
we get about acne OS we have a system
prompt we have a prompt that seems to be
doing decent enough but here we're going
to start layering on edge cases and
examples and so on so definitely want to
uh point you in that direction for a
really nice resource to practice with
those pieces we'll make sure you all
have a link to that GitHub um as we uh
as we get to wrap up
here going back to rag architecture and
tips I want to wrap up up with this
little piece here retrieval augmented
generation is a super super super super
super common term that you've heard in
this industry and if you have not heard
about it no worries I will explain the
idea the idea here is retrieving
information that your large language
model does not know about or may
partially know about so the most common
example is your company's data your
internal data your own personal family
history even things that are after the
time at which the model has been trained
so if that's after April 2024 or August
23 or whatever the cof date of training
is you might want to augment the
knowledge that your large language model
has with rag most of the work is done
with that R most of the work is done in
that retrieval the augmenting in
generation is simply just taking the
stuff you get back and generating a new
input so the RN rag is really where most
of the work is done but what's the
obvious Advantage here you want to start
using Claud for your own internal
companies's data or you want to make a
knowledge base of your company's
documentation obviously something that
Claude is not trained on this is how we
can augment the llm with external
knowledge a basic rag architecture looks
like this someone asks a question we
take that question and we generate an
embedding which is really just a list of
lots and lots and lots and lots and lots
and lots and lots of floating Point
numbers that represent the semantic
meaning of what we're looking for we
then try to find things that are similar
in semantic meaning in some kind of
database very commonly a vector database
we take all our information that is
external we put it in a vector database
we find similar records and then we take
that data and put it into our prompt and
now Claud can do all of its wonderful
work with this additional context this
is a very simple flow with a rag
architecture this can obviously scale
and get infinitely more complex here's a
basic idea of a rag architecture and rag
setup the things that you have to do to
get this to work you have to have some
information your company's documentation
your company's data your medical records
whatever it may be that you want to
vectorize and you got to put that in a
vector database you then have to take a
query that comes in and embed it using
some embedding model and similar and
find similar searches in your vector
database there are lots of different
tools for this there are lots of
different models that can do these
embeddings vertex has an entire Garden
of tools to help you here so this is
where you can really lean on the the
ecosystem that vertex has and many
different companies offer these
Solutions as we start to shift a bit
more in complexity something that we
haven't covered too much here that we
can maybe cover in a future section it's
the idea of tool use and Tool use is
instead of Claude saying something like
I don't know the answer we can tell
Claude hey if someone's asking about
something like what's the weather right
now or what is a great gift for a
five-year-old in my product catalog
instead of Claude saying I don't know
Claude can actually tell us as the
developer hey looks like someone's
trying to search for some products
here's a tool that I know about go do
what you want with it we can then
programmatically take that information
go ahead and call an API search things
in a database the reason why Rag and
Tool use are used together so commonly
is because many times you don't
necessarily need to jump for embedding
in a vector database and so on if
someone just ask Claude something like
who you know what what is the difference
between the number three and the number
seven Claude can probably give you a
decent answer for that if you ask Claude
a question like can you explain what a
large language model is you might not
need to go and do this embedding and
vectorization and so on so as you get
more comfortable with these pipelines
and these ideas a lot of times you don't
always have to jump for it so this is
just one example and hopefully in the
future session we can talk about tool
use and eals and all sorts of fun things
in this
ecosystem when you have external
documents and you feed them to Claude
the recommended format that we have is
to actually use these XML
tags
documents and then inside have a
document with a source and a document
content this sometimes takes a little
bit of finagling or working with code on
your end but this is how Claude has been
trained on many different kinds of
documents with these particular tags
this also allows you to add a particular
unique identifier for each parts of the
document you can put in your own
metadata as well but this can lead to
much more effective results from
retrieval from systems that Claude is
not aware of out of the box so just a
small little note if you're working with
rag with Claude this is a uh reference
for you to kind of think about that
ingesting and the right way to structure
your
data some tips in the rag ecosystem like
we mentioned the hardest things to do in
rag is the r that retrieval process if
someone puts in a really really really
really really long
query how are we going to figure out
what it is exactly that they're looking
for when we take our company's
documentation we can't just put all the
documentation in one record in the
database we have to break it up into
smaller chunks there's only so much that
we can embed at a time so how do we
preserve the semantic meaning how do we
preserve the order and the accuracy of
our data when we have to literally chop
it up and chop it up and chop it up that
process of chunking is something that
you want to be really mindful of and can
lead to lots of different kinds of
challenges in this ecosystem there's
another really interesting technique
that you can use in rag called reranking
which is where you can take the query
that you have or take the information
that the user is trying to search for
and you can rerank the results by having
a large language model try to rewrite
what the user is looking for to be more
accurate so you can actually use a large
language model to rewrite the query that
the user has to figure out a potential
different ranking for the best possible
option all slightly more advanced ideas
but things that you will probably come
across when hearing about rag hearing
this terminology and so
on rag has been kind of the deao
solution that many many many folks do
reach for but as we evolve in this
ecosystem kind of want to just put some
things in your brain for what might
change in the future as we go along so
as more optimizations come out external
knowledge search will absolutely improve
external knowledge search is a essential
part of what you do when working with
large language models can be great to
talk to an llm but if you're using this
for your company you're going to have
your own kind of knowledge that you need
to be retrieved rag is a great solution
out of the box but it runs into some
problems especially with making sure
you're getting accurate results making
sure you're being efficient in your
searching can be tweaked a lot but some
Alternatives as we start getting more
and more in this ecosystem prompt
caching is a technique that is becoming
more and more popular prompt caching is
the idea where we're sending really long
conversations we're putting lots of
information in the context but after
each message we have to recreate all
those tokens again we to generate all
those tokens again can we instead kind
of take a picture take a snapshot take
those tokens and store them in a cash so
that we don't have to keep tokenizing
regenerating tokens over and over and
over again this would allow us we put
lots of information in a prompt tons of
information that normally every time
might take too long to load but instead
we can take all this information we can
cash it so that when we look at it again
we're going to load it much much faster
so can you take some of that
documentation and instead of a external
data source you can just put it in the
prompt and cach it as larger context
Windows come in as the amount of total
amount of tokens that we can have over
the course of an entire conversation
grows we're getting to you know levels
of 100 of thousands million and so on
this might avoid the need for rag
because we can just put everything in
the context window as we have better
embedding models as we have different
kinds of data stores this will continue
to only improve so rag is something that
I don't know what it'll look like over
the next six months or year or so on but
it is constantly going through changes
iterations and
improvements all right we have some
awesome questions I can tell people are
really enjoying this session because
we've got some very specific questions
for you Ellie so I'll start with this
first one uh this was from Charlie and
Charlie asks what are some cool use
cases you've seen using prompt
engineering wow um cool use cases that
I've seen using prompt engineering there
is a uh a tremendous amount here I think
some of the most impressive things that
I've seen or some of the things that I'm
personally most excited about are the
medical field and the amount of research
that we can do or the Partnerships that
we can establish to drive Innovation
forward in the space to honestly just
make the world a better place in general
there is so much that is unknown and
there's only more that's going to be
known by using llms and such in terms of
the general day-to-day use cases for
things like prompt engineering we've
just seen so many customers go from
seeing data that they're not expecting
or things are not great or things are
hallucinating and just by following the
steps in the meta prompter
even just 10 15 minutes of triaging
debugging just leads to a completely
different result so the thing that I'm
actually excited about is just trying to
get people to not necessarily give up if
the llm is not giving you what you want
out of the box kind of lean into these
steps but long-term the medical space
shortterm just seeing customer customer
wins across so many different use cases
um customer support obviously chat Bots
are a big piece um Financial tools
there's just so much you can do here
yeah solving that issue of always having
to be like agent agent getting to those
answers uh more
efficiently all right this next one is
from John John asks is the prompt
engineering dashboard available for
professional accounts or business
accounts or is this a separate product
so the the the dashboard I guess that
you saw the kind of workbench and so on
um as long as you have an anthropic
account that is something that you can
use and whether you are part of cloud
for work or Enterprise or doing this
individually as long as you have an
account you can go ahead and use that
you'll need to set up a you know API key
for yourself there's some billing that
needs to happen but it is extremely easy
to get started for individuals and then
organizations can share those
workbenches as
well great this question is from Jan or
Yan perhaps uh do the prompt
improvements discussed here take part
when doing meta
prompting yeah absolutely that's a
fantastic question so we uh we have a
entire team focused on prompt engineer
Ing and research and all that they do is
really just try to meta prompt The Meta
prompt and figure out all different
kinds of ways especially as our models
evolve as our models get smarter as the
techniques that maybe once worked for
things like Claude one or two or 21 have
totally changed we are constantly
iterating on that meta prompter and
we've made the uh The Meta prompter
completely available it's a Jupiter
notebook you can find it in our
documentation so that's something that
we've you know shared with the entire
world but it's also something that we're
constantly iterating on so every day
every week or so there're always little
things little tweaks that we try to
think about to incorporate to just
deliver the best quality
prompts nice all right James asks how
would you apply vows to more complex
workflows such as multi-agent workflows
that utilize tools as part of the task
excellent excellent question um well you
have to you have to bring me back to
talk about evals but in this one
question I will I will definitely tell
you
there are lots of different ways for
doing evals there is the very tedious
human grading side of things which you
know even we point towards you want to
try to avoid that because it just
doesn't scale for things like
multi-agent use or step-by-step
processes the best thing to do is to
start with evals on each of those
individual levels because if the eval
for example is you expect some kind of
large agentic workflow to produce some
output and then the eval is just is the
output what I want unless you've set up
everything so prop L and correctly it's
unlikely that you're going to get the
results you want and then debugging and
triaging is going to be very difficult
so the same way that you would write
unit tests and then on top of that write
integration tests I would try to lean on
that same kind of philosophy and idea
when you are testing things again
depends on your use case sometimes
programmatically it can be as simple as
I expect that the output contains this
word I expect that the output contains
these particular pieces sometimes you
also need to use an llm to do some of
the grading as well so especially with
agentic workflows we've seen models
grading other models specifically models
with different tiers of intelligence
grading other models on certain parts of
the process so this is where the same
way that you have a agentic workflow
with lots of different steps you now
have an evaluation Suite with lots of
different steps checking things along
the way so that if the output is not
what you want you know kind of how
things are G to throughout that
process great all right we have a
question from Saba Saba asks Dynamic
content SL rag step two also covers
tools listing how about chat history
what should be the order of rag doc
Snippets tool function listing tool
return results and chat history
definitely so the the chat history um if
you if you have a a prompt and you're
then injecting the chat history that's a
little bit different if you have the
entire kind of back and forth
conversation the chat history is
preserved so I'll start kind of with the
tool side of things the tool definitions
come in when The Prompt is created so
there's a key called tools and you pass
in the definition of your tools but in
terms of what you want the ideal output
to look like with a particular tool or
you want to give some examples of what
that tool might look like that just goes
in the examples section so any
possibility for that endot or five shot
or 10 shot prompting think of those kind
of tools as the place to put that there
uh rag again kind of top of the document
and dynamic information that's where I
would put that content and then for the
chat history depending on kind of where
you're storing the history that might be
a little bit tricky but that also would
be kind of in your examples section so
breaking those breaking those three
areas apart is what I would
do great and then I think we have time
for one more question let's take this
one from Chris uh Chris asks does Claude
have a sense of how certain it is in its
answer can it give a useful confidence
score that's a fantastic fantastic
question so there is a tremendous amount
of research that we do about how Claud
gets to the answer the entire field of
interpretability trying to figure out
kind of what's Happening under the hood
at the neuron level right out of the box
there there is no way to have a kind of
confidence score and so on the way that
you can try to get more of those
accuracy scores are when you use tools
like rag where you can basically ask
from the query that the person has put
in what is the similarity to other
records that we have or other embeddings
that we have what is that kind of
similarity score and there's a metric
called cosine similarity there are a
couple other metrics that kind of give
you a level of accuracy or similarity
that's where you'll see a little bit
more of that kind of confidence score
like you know red or yellow or green or
a 66% chance that this is what you're
looking for but out of the box if you
ask Claud something and you say you know
on a scale to 10 zero to 10 how
confident are you um you're gonna have a
hard time kind of getting that uh that
measure to be pretty
sustainable I li we have time for one
more question so I'm going to sneak one
more in for you um this is from Linda
how does Claude handle potential
inconsistencies or contradictions in
retrieved
information these are excellent
questions so when there are potential
inconsistencies it's it's hard for Claud
to kind of know historically what all
the inconsistencies have been and such
so this kind of goes back to the this is
where the r in retrieval is a tricky
process this is where reranking can also
be really helpful but at the same time
you can still always ask Claude for site
site the sources make sure that the data
here has been backed by sources and show
me where you found these sources and
that's always a really helpful way to
kind of ground CLA in the truth the same
way that you want to just make sure that
if there's a world in which the answer
is not known you can have Cloud just
explicitly say I don't know and make
sure that that's part of your prompt as
well so it's a a slightly more difficult
thing to do past the retrieval stage
because that's really where the data is
being retrieved and it's hard for Quad
to say you're embedding model was wrong
that's not really possible but you can
still do your best to kind of stop
things and use claw as your last
defense great well I have learned so
much today thank you so much for sharing
all of these best practices any any
parting thoughts wisdom you want to
share with our audience uh about prompt
engineering anthropic XML
tags XL tags where um no I think the you
know follow that Golden Rule with
prompting really try to treat prompt
engineering as a science instead of an
art and if the first thing you get back
from the llm is not what you expect do
your best to not get too frustrated and
realize there's an entire world of
evolving to get what you're looking
for wonderful well thank you so much
Ellie and this has been so exciting to
have uh real use cases and examples
shown on the show so thank you so much
for speaking to our audience today and
I'm sure we gonna get a lot of folks uh
maybe tweeting you reaching out asking
questions um and that is the end of our
stream today thank you so much for
everybody who joined us live or if
you're joining us on demand in the in
the future hello uh and we will wrap up
today's session thanks everyone thank
you so much
[Music]
h
t
[Music]